{
  "GroupId": 5,
  "GroupName": "SPORTS",
  "Levels": [
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 1,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "CATCH",
          "question": "A moment's grasp, swift and sly"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "THEFT",
          "question": "Silent shadow, possessions drift"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "TENON",
          "question": "Wooden joint, strong and true, connecting pieces"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "TENES",
          "question": "connecting bone, where movement belongs"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "JOINT",
          "question": "Where bones meet, in flexible bind"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "VISIT",
          "question": "A welcomed presence, a cherished stay"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "TENNIS",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 2,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "FLOWER",
          "question": "Nature's artwork, in vibrant array"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "ORANGE",
          "question": "Sun-kissed hue, citrus delight, juicy sweetness"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "OXFORD",
          "question": "Scholar's haven, steeped in lore"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 1,
          "answer_text": "TICKET",
          "question": "Admission granted, to journeys near or far"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "OBJECT",
          "question": "shape and form, silent witness"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "TARGET",
          "question": "Hit your mark with precision"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "SILENT",
          "question": "In the absence of sound, it speaks volumes"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 2,
          "answer_text": "ONLINE",
          "question": "Navigate the virtual realm, where clicks replace footsteps"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "FOOTBALL",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 3,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "FABRICS",
          "question": "Threads of creativity weave together in this world of textures"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "DIAMOND",
          "question": "A gem of unparalleled brilliance, coveted by many for its timeless allure"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "ADDIDAS",
          "question": "Stride in style with this iconic brand"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "COMPANY",
          "question": "In the business of innovation, this entity orchestrates success with its vision"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "PRIVATE",
          "question": "Beyond public view, secrets are held close in this secluded realm"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "PENALTY",
          "question": "A consequence imposed for crossing lines"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "NATURAL",
          "question": "In the realm of Earth's raw beauty"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "SMOKING",
          "question": "this habit ignites debate while leaving a lingering haze of health concerns in its wake"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "MONITOR",
          "question": "Observing the digital landscape with vigilance"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "BADMINTON",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 4,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "KITCHEN",
          "question": "Where culinary dreams simmer and flavors blend"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "SUPPORT",
          "question": "An invisible pillar, it uplifts and strengthens"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "LOGICAL",
          "question": "In the realm of reason and order, this path unveils itself through rational steps"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "SPEAKER",
          "question": "Amplifying whispers into roars, this device breathes life into sound"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "PROJECT",
          "question": "From conception to completion, it's the blueprint of dreams realized"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 5,
          "answer_text": "SPRAYED",
          "question": "Invisible strokes paint the air, leaving a scent of change"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 0,
          "answer_text": "HOCKEY",
          "question": null
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "GroupId": 5,
      "LevelId": 5,
      "Questions": [
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "MOBILITY",
          "question": "Freedom's ally, it unlocks horizons and paves paths to new frontiers"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "GRAPHICS",
          "question": "\"Visions manifest in pixels"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "HISTORIC",
          "question": "In the footprints of time, it echoes tales of yore"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "LAKEVIEW",
          "question": "Perched on nature's edge, it offers a panoramic vista of serene waters"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "PRESSURE",
          "question": "Invisible weight, it pushes and molds"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 3,
          "answer_text": "INTERNET",
          "question": "An infinite web of connection, where bytes traverse borders and ideas flow freely"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "KEYBOARD",
          "question": "Tap into the gateway of expression, where words dance at your fingertips"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "PARALLEL",
          "question": "In the realm of geometry, it's lines running side by side"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "ISOLATED",
          "question": "In solitude's embrace, it stands alone"
        },
        {
          "level_image": 4,
          "answer_text": "TAILORED",
          "question": "Custom fit for elegance, it drapes with precision"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}